Damn it all! This is bad!
I have to let Yoshikage know!
It's Reimi!
Hey Rohan, did you take
the pictures in this album?
I did, why?
I assume there's a reason
this one is marked.
What's so special about it?
You seem to have homed
in on this little boy.
Oh yeah.
I'm not too concerned with him.
He seemed to be sneaking around the
area so I thought I'd document him.
But look, the boy's
name is Hayato Kawajiri.
He has the same surname as this man.
Really? He does? Yeah. Check it out.
Weren't you investigating this person?
Mm-hmm.
He was one of many potential suspects.
If Rohan Kishibe uncovers the truth,
it's over for my darling Yoshikage!
Hayato! Hayato!
Damn it.
This is the last time I'll say it, Hayato!
Answer me when I call you!
Oh, it's you, dear.
Sorry for all the commotion.
I could have sworn it
was Hayato in the bath.
Honestly, what are we
going to do with that boy?
Look at this place.
His clothes are scattered around
the hallway like a bomb went off.
I wish he'd take after
you a little bit more.
He could be such a slob.
Not to mention he's ignoring me.
Though if I know him, he's probably
reading manga with his headphones on again.
Honey, what happened?
You've got blood on your fingers.
Let me take care of that.
You don't want it to get infected.
No, I'll take care of it myself.
I just need a simple bandage.
I can handle that.
Oh.
I just caught my fingers in the door.
It's no big deal, really.
I'll see you
next time.
Good days!
Hayato Kawajiri?
So you think this grade school
kid has something to do with Kira?
Well, at this point, we're not
totally sure if they're connected.
That said, Rohan-sensei
thinks he's onto something.
I agree.
A grade school kid taking
videos of his dad on
the down low sends up
some serious red flags.
We're talking about meeting
up tomorrow morning.
Once we've gone through everything,
we'll head over to Hayato
Kawajiri's house together.
Rohan-sensei said he's already
figured out the address.
That artsy asshole doesn't
miss a beat, does he?
Well, count me in.
Oh, and I should ask Okuyasu, right?
And Jotaro, too.
Can't forget about him.
You can leave getting in touch with Mr.
Jotaro to me.
All right, we'll see you
tomorrow at 8.30 a .m.
Just look for the big Pepsi sign.
Right, got it.
Pepsi at 8.30.
That means I'm gonna be late for school.
Even so, if things pan out the way Rohan
hopes, it'll be worth the tardy slip.
Are you okay?
I can tell there's
something wrong, sweetie.
You're all pale and sweaty.
It's nothing.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm just in some pain is all.
I did just slam my fingers.
Now please, go downstairs
and make some tea.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay, dear.
I know this is gonna sound totally
random, but well, I don't know.
You've had this vibe
like you'll live forever
The tea will be ready soon
If you so much as lay a single
finger on me your whole cover
will be blown sky-high Stay the
hell away from me and my mom!
It's non-negotiable, you got that?
Stay away or I reveal everything!
You're adorably naive!
As if I'd let someone find me out!
Getting rid of that Hayato brat
was the very height of foolishness!
You of all people should have known that!
Quiet, I'm trying to think
of a way out of this!
Don't waste time, it's
too late for that now!
You did a remarkable job of making it
look as though he fell and hit his head.
But your timing really
couldn't have been worse.
Rohan Kishibe has already begun his
investigation into Hayato Kawajiri.
They don't know for sure yet that
Kosaku Kawajiri is Yoshikage Kira.
But they're coming here tomorrow
to find out once and for all.
Sanyu mustn't remain in
this house a minute longer.
Will you stop talking?
I'm trying to think.
Even when you were a boy,
when things didn't go your way and
you felt the world was against you,
you'd always bite your nails
till your fingers were raw.
My poor sweet boy.
Oh, the misery you must be suffering.
We've run out of options here, kiddo.
You must leave this wretched
town behind for good.
If you get out now, you still have a chance
to escape and hold on to your anonymity.
Are you seriously asking me to
run away and abandon Morioh?
Living every moment in
excruciating secrecy is one of
the most horrible experiences
a person can go through,
and I refuse to go back to that hell.
I swear I will never leave this town.
What the hell?
The arrow moved on its own, but
I swear I didn't do anything.
I wasn't even touching it!
What's it doing?
No! Yoshikage!
Hiato! Hiato!
Just how long are you gonna sleep in?
It's time to get up and...
Hayato, why didn't you tell
me you were out of bed?
You startled me.
Come down for breakfast
and answer when I call you.
I had a terrible night's sleep.
That jerk-faced imposter found out I
witnessed one of his murders and assaulted me.
For now, I've made sure he can't
do anything to hurt me or mom.
But that's a temporary solution.
He'll find a way around that.
I don't understand!
What in the world's gotten
into you, Yoshikage?
You've been acting
strange since last night.
Don't ignore me!
I don't know why, but Rohan Kishibe is now
keen on snooping around Hayato Kawajiri.
We've run out of time, son.
They're coming to search
the house tomorrow.
Hmm.
There's no cause for alarm.
But Yoshikage!
My deadly queen has
acquired a third ability.
Huh?
What's going on here?
What could have happened to make you
so lackadaisical all of a sudden?
Miso-marinated cow tongue.
You're kidding.
Why didn't you say we were on the air?
Good morning, all.
It's 7.55.
Time for today's
prefectural weather report.
Today, we'll be enjoying
sunny skies. Hi-ya, Toe.
Hayato, are you listening?
Answer the phone!
His attitude has completely
changed since that bath last night.
What happened between now and then?
Hayato, what are you doing?
The damn phone isn't gonna
answer itself, you know!
My favorite China tea set!
This is all your fault!
Why do you ignore me?
Don't you have any
respect for your mother?
Admit it!
You only see me as a
nuisance who gets in the way!
Well, fine! I'm done!
Now, now.
Let's not start the day with an argument.
If it can't be fixed,
I'll buy you another one.
This is the Kawajiri residence.
No, I'm afraid not.
It was the wrong number, that's all.
And Hayato's going through a quiet phase.
No need to fret.
We're a family.
We should support each other,
not tear each other down.
Let's all work on that.
Speaking of work, I should get going.
But before I head off,
I'd like to steal a kiss.
Have a nice day.
Thank God, he took off.
No, I'm right here.
Why don't we walk together for a bit?
One moment I'm in the throes of despair.
Now I'm on top of the world.
So much has happened so very quickly.
It's been an absolute
whirlwind of emotion.
But now, at long last, I'll be able to
live a life free of worry and anxiety.
You really put the pressure on last
night, but because of you, I've matured.
You were so extraordinarily determined,
especially for a tank your age.
It's incredible that you
threatened Yoshikage Kira.
What?
Yoshikage Kira?
Looks like I just told you my name.
Does this mean you're
going to kill me after all?
Kill you?
Simply because you know my secret?
There's no need for that.
Like I said, I've matured.
It doesn't matter what
you or anyone else does.
No one in the world can rival me now.
You no longer arouse any interest in me.
And if I wanted to kill you, I would
have simply finished the job last night.
We're all going to get along
just fine, I guarantee it.
So take a breath, kiddo.
We're family.
Well, Daddy Dearest is off to the station.
Do your best at school today, Hayato.
No one can rival him?
Rival?
That means there must be
other people walking around
out there with the same
kind of bizarre powers.
Still, his confidence is terrifying.
He's brazenly calling
himself unrivaled now.
Does that mean he gained some new power?
What do I do now?
Damn it!
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do!
Hey, you're Hayato Kawajiri. Huh?
Aren't you?
I've been waiting for you.
My name is Rohan Kishibe, and
I have a question for you.
Do us both a favor and answer it.
It's about this picture.
This is you, isn't it?
And you were taking a video of
your dad in the back there, right?
Wait.
What is this?
I know that was unexpected.
Questioning him would be troublesome.
Reading his mind will be much more
efficient when it comes to this endeavor!
Not to mention it'll be far
more accurate than a Q A?
Huh?
Why would that be in his pages?
The only thing Heaven's Door
should be revealing is a candid,
honest, written account of this boy's
life memories And yet, there's a warning?
What's going on?
This warning here, is it part
of the boy's life experience?
When I drove over today, I wasn't planning
on giving him more than a quick peruse.
But now he's got me strangely hooked.
Do not read on. Hmm.
I wonder who that could be for.
What is all this?
This makes even less sense.
What does it mean?
Damn it all
This kid who the hell is he?
Come on the weather report
never said anything about rain
No way, a 27.
Who is this Hayato Kawajiri, and
how does he experience the future?
Could he be a stand user?
Calm down.
No way this is a stand ability.
Heaven's Door can't read the future.
It just reveals what
one has seen and heard.
I'm certain the explanation would
be somewhere in these pages.
Kira.
It's all coming together.
This little kid, he's a jackpot.
I finally found him.
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri.
He disguised himself as this kid's father.
Then Rohan Kishibe was also killed.
The new super-powered Kira
found a way to murder him.
Deadly queen bomb type 3 bites the dust.
Heaven's door attack.
Deadly queen has already
entered your pupil.
Rohan Kishibe.
No, you're not seeing things.
Deadly queen's bomb type 3
has already been activated.
Your time is come?
And there you have it.
Deadly Queen's new power will annihilate
all who attempt to take me down.
It's a bomb that will activate in anyone
who dares approach Hayato to get to me.
Hayato's verbalizing my true
name will also activate the bomb,
as will putting my name in writing.
In other words, my new bomb
has been planted in Hayato.
I just remembered.
I promised to meet Koichi.
He and the others will be here at 8.30.
Excellent.
I've done it.
I rooted out Yoshikage Kira.
I know who he is now.
Koichi will be here soon.
I have to let him know. I must.
Over here.
I finally found him.
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri.
Evan's door sniffed him out.
You have to hear this!
Can you hear me?
Koichi!
And now, gaze upon the glory
that is Nedley Queen Bob-type 3!
Koichi!
Aaaaaahhhh!
Was I dreaming?
I had a terrible night's sleep.
It was one horrible dream
after another. Hayato!
Just how long are you gonna sleep in?
It's time to get up and...
Hayato, why didn't you tell
me you were out of bed?
You startled me.
Come down for breakfast
and answer when I call you.
It's crazy.
But I...
You're kidding.
Why didn't you say we were on...
Wait, I've seen this newscast.
Hayato?
Hayato, are you listening?
Answer the phone.
This isn't a dream.
None of what just happened was a dream.
This is the same morning.
Everything is repeating.
Somehow I'm reliving the
same morning from yesterday.
Which means that guy's real
name is Yoshikage Kira.
He's behind all this.
This is what he meant by being unrivaled.
He's done something to
me with his new power.
Hayato, what are you doing?
The damn phone isn't going
to answer itself, you know!
Oh, yeah!
Watch it!
Ow!
Nice catch, Hayato.
It's almost like you knew
I was going to drop it.
But you could try answering me next time.
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
So I'm the only one who knows
this morning already happened.
And for everyone else,
it's business as usual.
It's like you knew she
was going to drop it, eh?
It appears you've returned from a long day
of blasting your friend to kingdom come,
Hayato.
Truthfully,
I'm not actually privy to all the gory
details of your little foray today.
But Deadly Queen's new power
is called Bites the Dust.
It automatically protects me
from right inside your body.
So thank you, Hayato.
Tell me, are you even aware that I killed
you last night when we were in the bath?
At that moment, it was as if the fates
themselves had witnessed my despair,
and I was granted a gift in
the form of this ability.
I tried the ability out on you, and
miraculously time reversed course one hour.
The reality that I'd
murdered you was no more.
At the same time, you also became
my personal life-protecting bomb.
You told one of them about me,
thereby activating the bomb
and sending you back here.
So, who did you annihilate, hmm?
I won't tell.
Who did you murder?
No, you got it wrong.
I didn't tell anyone anything.
Of course not, which tells me you were
interrogated by Rohan Kishibe, no doubt.
Even if you never think about tattling,
a simple inquiry into the
identity of yours truly will
be enough to activate the
horrors of Bites the Dust.
After which, you'll incinerate
the offender and zip back here.
Your visit with Rohan Kishibe is
now a figment of your imagination.
So now you know the
power it bites the dust.
My true name will never cross your lips.
And no soul will live long
enough to seek me out.
We'll come and stand a little bit
closer, breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I
need you, but ooh, I gotta find you.
Ooh,
I want you, I don't know if I need
you, but ooh, I gotta find you.
I'll break it down.
Let's rock out.